The Stage Is Set... And The Dinner Is Served.
Grizzly II: Revenge is a horror, music, thriller film directed by André Szöts.
All hell breaks loose when a giant grizzly, reacting to the slaughter of her cubs
by poachers, attacks a massive rock concert in the National Park.
[This sequel to "Grizzly" (1976) was left unfinished after production wrapped prematurely in 1983, and was not officially
released until 2020, though a bootleg workprint version had been in circulation for some years prior to this.]
Nick Hollister, played by Steve Inwood.
Samantha Owens, played by Deborah Raffin.
Bouchard, played by John Rhys-Davies.
Eileene Draygon, played by Louise Fletcher.
Ron, played by George Clooney.
Tina, played by Laura Dern.
Grizzly II: Revenge (sometimes stylized Grizzly II.
Revenge, also known as Grizzly II: The Predator and Grizzly II.
The Concert) is a 1983 American action thriller horror film
that was not properly released until 2020.
It was directed by André Szöts and is a sequel to the 1976 film
Grizzly directed by William Girdler and David Sheldon.
The film is about a giant grizzly named Tawanda who seeks
revenge after her cub is killed by poachers.
It stars Steve Inwood, Louise Fletcher, John Rhys-Davies, Deborah Raffin and Deborah Foreman; actors George Clooney,
Laura Dern, and Charlie Sheen, who were all relatively unknown at the time, all had small roles in the film.
Originally filmed in Hungary in 1983, the release
was put on hold for many decades.
The film premiered at the 2020 Hollywood Reel Independent Film Festival and
was released on January 8, 2021, through video-on-demand.
The film explores themes of concert, panic, sequel, wild animal, bear.
The tone is dark and intense.